hi viewers welcome to end our video
Welcome to mng jazba TV
today we will go about the next topic
about Sun life and health insurance
company
in most countries especially us
executor's office is a home office you
can see now their address
so
you can visit also www.com celllife.com
after
discuss our topic Please Subscribe our
Channel
thank you now we will start our topic
Sun Life
what is Sun life and health insurance
company
Sun life and health insurance company
certifies that it is issued and
delivered Group Insurance to be a
policyholder shown below policy number
that you can see in your screen police
effective date it is called the screen
and the certificate contains the terms
of the group insurance policies that
your facts
Insurance the City skate is part of a
group insurance policy this certificate
is a governor by the laws of the issue
date shown above all this otherwise
painted by the federal employee
retirement income and security of Raisa
signed from the company David J Holly
present
now we will discuss about the tables of
the contents number one sections
of employee Insurance 3 termination of a
benefit
provision of the policy 4 covered imply
basically insurance benefit fives claim
proficient 6. Insurance con
continuations seven probability add
continuity of coverage H9 General
persistence
benefits highlights eligible classes all
part of United States local 153
employees working in the United States
schedule to work at 25 hours per week
the all full-time United States
employees working in the United States
scheduled to work at least 35 hours per
week eligibility waiting periods are
eligible to part-time local 153
employees until
the first of the month falling five year
of employment and
at all other eligible employees
until the first month conscient
coincident
with our next following date of employee
number one benefit highlights
classification one all eligible
part-time local 153 employees amount of
insurance fifty thousand dollars
included added certificate of the class
protability
waves of Premium contributions the cost
of your employee basic life insurance is
paid entirely by your employer this is
your non-contibility insurance
benefit highlights employ basic life
insurance
classification to all other eligible
employees amount of insurance fifty
thousand dollars included in certificate
for the class protability
waiver of premium contribution the cost
of employee basic life insurance is paid
entirely by your employer this is your
non-contributory insurance definitions
actually activity
actively at work means that you perform
all the regular duties of your job for a
fully worked day add your employee
normal place of business aside approved
or your employer or site where you
employ a business requires you to up
travel
you are considered actively to
work if you are usually perform the
regular duties of your job at your home
as long you can perform hard regularly
all regular duties of your job for full
work day
could
do at your employer normal place of
business you are considered actively to
work one day that is not your regular
schedule or work
as long as your activity to work
immediately preciously scheduled work
day and you are neither confined or
disabled
due to an injury and sickness
beneficially means the person person or
entity other than the employer until
receive that benefit proceed as they
become the under policy I'm beneficially
must be named by your writing in manner
acceptable to us
that is to sign on the file of the
employer
confine and confinement means confined
at a hospital or similar facility
domestic pattern means person who
together with the person
or the same of
opposite sex
definition 2 Mutual Grant of durable
power of attorney Mutual ground of
authority to make help decision health
and power of maturity ability by the
credit Creator or other individual able
to testify testify to Partners Financial
inter depends other items or prove
sufficient to establish economics
interdependency under the circumstances
of the particle case
eligibility waiting period means the
length of the most remember eligible
class before you can apply of insurance
the legibility waiting period is shown
benefit highlights employee means a
person who is employed by owner of
within the United States scheduled to
work at least minimum how well shown in
benefit highlights paid work earning in
the according the
applyable States provincial and final
wage on our laws has a ligamate federal
tax identifications numbers employee
does not include a section sessional or
temporarily employ whose annual work
schedule is less than 12th month during
our calendar year if you are employed
and you are working on a temporary
assignment outside of the United States
of 12th month or less you will be deemed
to be working within the United States
if you are an employee you are working
on a timely assigned outside of the
United States for more 12 months you
will not be considered unemployed under
the policy unless agree in writing
employer means employee import the
coverage page
of the certificates and they includes
any subsequently or Affiliated company
name in the application family members
mean
your suppose civil union partner or
domestic partners and be the following
relatives for your suppose civil union
Partners or
domestic partner one parents two
grandparents Childs and grandchildren
brothers and sister they include adopted
law in the step relatives Hospital means
the faciality lesson in the applicable
just addiction that provides need icon
queer and treatment to seek an injured
person on a inpatient basis with 24 hour
nursing Services by a under the
supervision of physician injury means
bodily empowerment layer of means that
you are temporal is not activated to at
work or for a period of time your
employer agreed in the country
aggregate in the writing
your normal vacation time is not
considered offered temporary life leave
of absence and the material of the
subsidiary two it is the best you can
listen and you it is very beneficial for
you leave of absence mean that you are
temporarily not actively to upwork for
period After Time employer agreed in
writing your normal vacation time is not
considered a temporarily leave of
absence
material and substantial duties means
the essential task function skills and
responsibilities required by employee
for the performance of an occupation
material and substation duties mean
those who job May takes that are
required to a particular job performed
in the general labor market and National
economy and cannot be reasonable
modified or permitted
now we will discuss about insurance
continuations or there are the condition
under which your employer can continue
your insurance while the policy is
enforced that subjects the condition
states in the policy your employer may
continue your insurance that doesn't
work no has no force on the date
immediately
before the date you cause the activity
to work by paying the required minimum
to us for any of the following reasons
and durations absence due to injury or
sickness up to 12 months layoff up to
one month thanks for watching now today
now
who will continue our topic in the next
video
wait for my attempts thank you please
like And subscribe our Channel if you
like our videos
on the next we will discuss about
the some points about insurance
continuation
thank you